Mupa M'mbetsa Nzaphila

Full Stack Developer

mupasmail@gmail.com +491624735101 • Mannheim, Germany

www.mupanzaphila.com in www.linkedin.com/in/mupa-nzaphila

www.github.com/Mupa1

A dedicated full stack developer with about 3 years of experience building intuitive, interactive, responsive websites, and web applications. Proficient in Node.js, React, Next.js, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and TypeScript. Committed to staying up-to-date with the latest web development technologies and best practices.

Professional Experience

Frontend Engineer, ACCURE Battery Intelligence *⊘*

10/2023 - 05/2024

- Developed 100% of the frontend of a new product optimized for performance using React.js.
- Improved overall design of an existing platform enhancing UX and increasing conversion rates by 35%.
- Daily maintained code, debugged and solved issues, ensuring 100% platform stability.
- Collaborated with 2 backend developers to integrate frontend components with RESTful APIs, ensuring 100% data consistency and reliability.

Frontend Engineer, HEYCAR ⊘

10/2021 - 09/2023

- Created UI components and configurable reusable input elements that reduced code repetition by 40% on the global commerce checkout.
- Collaborated with designers to ensure the technical feasibility of 15+ UI/UX designs.
- Daily maintained code, debugged and solved issues, ensuring 100% platform stability.
- Increased unit test coverage by 30% on the financing calculator micro-frontend which led to timesaving as bugs got detected early in development.

Education

Full Stack Web Development, MICROVERSE ∅

01/2020 - 02/2021

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Databases

Front End Development, Udacity ⊘

11/2019 - 11/2019

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS

Skills

Languages — JavaScript, TypeScript, Ruby, GraphQL, HTML, CSS, SASS

Frameworks & Libraries — React.js, Next.js, Redux, TailwindCSS, Material-UI, Styled Components, Framer Motion, Node.js

Tools & Platforms — Appwrite, Figma, Storybook, Webpack, Vite, Contentful, Git, GitHub, GitLab

Methods — UI Design, Unit Testing, Refactoring, Deployment, CI/CD, Accessibility, UI/UX, Responsive Design, Cross-browser Compatibility